<s:Envelope xmlns:s="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/soap/envelope/">
  <s:Header>
    <ActivityId CorrelationId="9e12760b-1965-421c-8f3d-9c950ca83a8b"
      xmlns="http://schemas.microsoft.com/2004/09/ServiceModel/Diagnostics">00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</ActivityId>
  </s:Header>
  <s:Body>
    <StartDisputeResponse xmlns="https://consumerconnectws.tui.transunion.com/">
      <StartDisputeResult xmlns:a="https://consumerconnectws.tui.transunion.com/data"
        xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
        <a:AccountName>CC2PartnerTesting1</a:AccountName>
        <a:ErrorResponse i:nil="true" />
        <a:RequestKey>15ac2bb6-eef7-4cad-b269-0f9001e57618</a:RequestKey>
        <a:ResponseType>Success</a:ResponseType>
        <a:ClientKey>VR_2019-06-25_13-38-16_ERMA</a:ClientKey>
        <a:DisputeStatus>
          <a:DisputeStatusDetail>
            <a:ClosedDisputes>
              <a:EstimatedCompletionDate>6/26/2019</a:EstimatedCompletionDate>
              <a:LastUpdatedDate>1/1/0001</a:LastUpdatedDate>
              <a:OpenDate>1/1/0001</a:OpenDate>
              <a:RequestedDate>1/1/0001</a:RequestedDate>
              <a:TotalClosedDisputedItems>0</a:TotalClosedDisputedItems>
              <a:TotalDisputedItems>1</a:TotalDisputedItems>
              <a:TotalOpenDisputedItems>0</a:TotalOpenDisputedItems>
            </a:ClosedDisputes>
            <a:DisputeId>6539</a:DisputeId>
            <a:LetterStatus>
              <a:DisputeLetterCode>PVC_FIN 000960022004 - Dispute Status ERMA J JONES</a:DisputeLetterCode>
              <a:DisputeLetterContent>We appreciate you taking the time to contact us at TransUnion.
                Our goal is to maintain complete and accurate credit
                information. It's our commitment to you.

                You recently submitted a dispute to TransUnion for an item(s) on
                your credit report. Our records show that we previously completed
                an investigation of the below item(s) and the data furnisher(s)
                verified the information on your credit file.

                As outlined in the Fair Credit Reporting Act, unless you have
                additional relevant information that supports the change you are
                requesting (i.e., a letter from the creditor or courthouse,
                billing statement, letter from the IRS, cancelled check or money
                order showing payment, etc.), we are not required to
                reinvestigate the same item(s) again at this time. If you do have
                additional information to support your dispute, you may upload it
                via transunion.com/dispute and we will conduct a reinvestigation.

                ROCKLAND TRUST
                Acct#: 6X0X7X1X0****
                288 UNION ST
                ROCKLAND, MA 02370
                (800) 528-7000



                If you disagree with this result, you may add a consumer
                statement of 100 words or less to your credit report explaining
                the details of why you disagree. Please note: if you provide a
                consumer statement containing medical information, you expressly
                consent to allow TransUnion to include this information in every
                credit report we issue about you. You may also contact the data
                furnishers directly to discuss the item(s) using the contact
                information provided above.

                If your dispute included additional items not listed above,
                that means we are conducting an investigation by:

                1. Making changes to your credit report based on the information
                you provided; OR
                2. Submitting an investigation request to the data furnisher(s)
                who provided the information

                Once the investigation is complete, you will receive the results
                for those additional items in a separate communication that will
                include your file number 960022004.

                We're here to help. Should you have any further questions please
                contact us at:
                -  www.transunion.com
                -  (800) 916-8800
                -  P.O. Box 2000
                  Chester, PA 19016-2000

                Please have your file number ready 960022004.

                Please do not reply to this email as this is a system generated
                email.
              </a:DisputeLetterContent>
            </a:LetterStatus>
            <a:Status>cancelledDispute</a:Status>
          </a:DisputeStatusDetail>
        </a:DisputeStatus>
      </StartDisputeResult>
    </StartDisputeResponse>
  </s:Body>
</s:Envelope>